​If you guys ever see me in real life.
如果你们在现实生活中见到我
Don't be scared to come up to say "hi".
不要害怕过来和我打招呼
I feel like I already know you guys.
我感觉我早就认识你们了
So we gotta cherish the memory by taking a selfie.
所以我们一定要自拍一张来纪念这美好的时刻
Seoul is known for its creative restaurants, for example
首尔以它富有创意的餐厅而闻名   例如
MIES container is like the "hooters" for women
MIES集装箱餐厅就像女士的猫头鹰餐厅
instead of gorgeous gals serving you up wings.
但没有漂亮女孩戴着翅膀为你服务
You have super cute guys
取而代之的是超级可爱的男孩
glistening while frying up your order.
为你准备菜肴时所散发出来那种魅力
So this is a fun place for not only ladies but couples.
这个有趣的地方不仅仅欢迎女士也欢迎情侣
Greasy, cheesy pizza, light dishes and fries,
油腻的芝士披萨   好吃的小碟和炸薯条
what's not to like?
有什么原因不喜欢呢